Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. William Woodville Rockhill papers (MS Am 2121): Guide.
William Woodville Rockhill papers,
- I. Correspondence and other papers
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno. Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 24 Apr 1893., (2946); ([1]p.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 17 Sep 1884., (2946a); ([4]p.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno. Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 8 Feb 1895., (2947); ([2]p.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno. Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 13 Feb 1895., (2948); ([2]p.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Tientsin, [1896] ([4]p,), (2948a)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno. Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 29 Jul 1896., (2949); ([2]p.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(LiHan, Chan) to [John] Russell Young; Philadelphia, 31 Jul [1886]., (2949a); (2l.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno. Russell Young) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 2 Aug 1896., (2950); ([2]p.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno. Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 2 Aug 1896., (2951); ([2]p.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 19 Oct 1896., (2951a); ([4]p.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Young; Philadelphia, 30 Oct 1896., (2951b); ([3]p.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.N.s.(JnoRussell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 23 Nov 1896., (2951c); 1l.
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno. Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 21 Dec 1896., (2952); ([1]p.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno. Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 26 Sep 1896., (2953); 1l.
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno. Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 15 Jan 1897., (2954); 2l.
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno. Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 12 Feb 1897., (2955); 1l.
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno. Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [Washington,] 26 Mar [1897]., (2956); 1l.
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(John Russell Young) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 20 May 1897., (2957); ([2]p.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(Jno Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 12 Aug 1897[?]., (2957a); (2l.)
  - Young, John Russell, 1840-1899. A.L.s.(JnoRussell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 15 Feb 1896., (2957b); (2l.)
  - Young, May (Dow) Russell. A.L.s.(May D. Russell Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; "The Lenox"; 7 Mar 1905., (2958); ([3]p.)
  - Young, Tsung S. Typed L.s.(T. S. Young) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 26 May 1914., (2959); 1l.
  - Yu Chung Han. A.L.s.(Yu Chung Han) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Moukden, 14 Jan 1914., (2960); ([2]p.)
  - Yule, Sir Henry, 1820-1889. A. Postcard s.(H. Yule) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [London,] 26 Sep [1883]., (2961); [1]p.
  - Yule, Sir Henry, 1820-1889. A.L.s.(H. Yule) to [Reinhold] Rost; Whitehall, 18 Jan [1888]., (2962); 1l.
  - Yule, Sir Henry, 1820-1889. A.L.s.(H. Yule) to [Reinhold] Rost; [n.p.] 28 Nov [1889]., (2963); 1l.
  - Yuan Shih-Kai, 1859-1916. Cablegram s.(Yuan Shih Kai) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Peking 9 Dec 1914., (2964); 1l.
  - Yuan Shih-Kai, 1859-1916. Transcript of L.s.(Yuan Shih-Kai) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [n.p. 15 May [?], (2965); 2l.
  - Yuan Shih-Kai, 1859-1916. Typescript of memorial of Yuan Shih-Kai and others in re abolition of system of examinations; [n.p.] 2 Sep 1905., (2966); 3l.
  - Yuan, Yuen Tai. A.L.s.(Yuan Yuen Tai) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p., n.d.], (2967); ([1]p.)
  - Yuan, Yuen Tai. A.L.s.(Yuan Yuen Tai) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 13 Jun 1909., (2968); ([2]p.)
  - Yuan, Yuen Tai. Cablegram s.(Yuan Yuen Tai) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Peking 15 Dec 1914., (2969); 1l.
  - Zabriskie, George. A.L.s.(George Zabriskie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Sands Point, 26 Jul 1900., (2970); ([3]p.)
- II. Unidentified material
  - Unidentified. Ms. Article (unsigned); [n.p., n.d.], (2971); 1l.
  - Unidentified. Ms. Article (unsigned); [n.p., n.d.], (2972); ([4]p.)
  - Unidentified. Ms. Article on "Slavery";[n.p., n.d.], (2973); ([15]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(?) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 6 May [1904]., (2974); ([3]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.(unsigned) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Constantinople, 11 Mar 1914., (2975); ([4]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.(unsigned) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Tiflis, 7 May 1913., (2976); ([3]p.)
  - Unidentified. Typed Document s.(?); [n.p.] 7 [?] 1913., (2977); ([1]p.)
    With envelope In Russian.
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(The Mouse) to William [Woodville Rockhill]; [n.p.] 24 Dec [1912], (2978); ([4]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(M. L. H. T.) to [?]; [n.p., 1898), (2979); ([3]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(Angee) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Duchess Co., New York, 15 Sep [1898]., (2980); ([4]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(Lina) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Madison, 16 Jul 1912., (2981); ([4]p.)
  - Unidentified. Telegram filled out in ms.(unsigned) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 7 Nov 1901., (2982); 1l.
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(T. Norton Longman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 5 Dec. 1889., (2983); [2]p.
  - Unidentified. A. Note s.(J. E.) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p., 1880], (2984); [1]p.
  - Unidentified. Typed L.s.(Charles) to William [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 5 Mar 1913., (2985); 1l.
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(?) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 31 Aug 1901., (2986); ([3]p.)
  - Unidentified. Typed Document s.(?) to [?]; [n.p.] 1913., (2987); 1l.
    With envelope. In Russian.
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(?) to "Dear Edward" [?]; [n.p.] 14 Mar [1873]., (2988); 1l.
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(?) to [?]; Berlin, 18 Mar 1899., (2989); ([2]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(?) to [?]; [n.p.] 14 May 1911., (2990); ([2]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(?) to [?]; Peking, 21 Aug 1901., (2991); ([2]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.(unsigned) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.], 14 May 1896., (2992); ([4]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.(unsigned) to "My dear Scott"[?]; Seoul, 7 Dec 1898., (2993); [2]p.
  - Unidentified. Typed L.(unsigned) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 17 May 1904., (2994); 1l.
  - Unidentified. Typed L.(unsigned) to William Woodville Rockhill; Geneva, 9 Apr 1914., (2995); 1l.
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(Sue) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Biarritz, 14 Oct [1913]., (2996); ([3]p.)
  - Unidentified. Typed L.(unsigned) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 23 Apr 1911., (2997); 1l.
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(E. S.) to "Lord Cuzzon"; [n.p., Dec 1902], (2998); ([3]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(?) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 23 Feb 1902., (2999); ([5]p.)
  - Unidentified. Ms. Poem beginning "Sweet flow'r, fair emblem of my lovely maid" etc.; [n.p., n.d.], (3000); 1l.
  - Unidentified. A.L.(unsigned) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 15 Jul 1911., (3001); [2]p.
  - Unidentified. Particle of L.(unsigned) to [?]; [n.p., 1911], (3002); [2]p.
    In French. The beginning and end parts of this letter are wanting.
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.(Charles) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Washington, 4 Apr [?], (3003); ([6]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.[C. A. S. R.) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cairo, 13 Dec 1902., (3004); ([4]p.)
  - Unidentified. Ms. Poem beginning "The spider built her lonely home" etc. in 4 verses; [n.p., n.d.], (3005); ([1]p.)
  - Unidentified. Typescript of L.(unsigned) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 14 Feb 1906., (3006); 5l.
  - Unidentified. Typedcript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to Bellamy Storer; Washington, 11 Feb 1897., (3007); 1l.
  - Unidentified. Ms. Document. In Chinese. With envelope., (3008)
  - Unidentified. Typed Article (unsigned); [n.p., n.d.], (3009); ([3]p.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.( ? ) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Tientsin, 17 Dec [1884]., (3009a); (2l.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.( ? ) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Berlin, 1 Jul 1893., (3009b); ([2]p.)
  - Unidentified. Typescript (c.c.) of L.(unsigned) to the Honorable..The Secretary of State; [n.p.] 11 Mar 1912., (3009c); 5l.
  - Unidentified. Typescript (c.c.) of L. (The American Group) to The Honorable. .. The Secretary of State; [n.p.] 17 Nov 1914., (3009d); 3l.
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.([ ? ] Linnier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 26 Mar [1886]., (3009e); (2l.)
  - Unidentified. A.L.s.([ ? ]) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; 29 [ ? ] 1887., (3009f); ([3]p.); In French.
- III. Miscellanea
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Mission to study governmental reforms"; Peking, 16 Jul 1905., (3010); 4l.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. "Abolishment of torture and inspection of jails"; [Peking] 25 Apr 1905., (3011); 1l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Uniform Weights and Measures"; Peking, 9 Oct 1907., (3012); 1l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Extracts from the History of the Wu-t'ai shan"; [n.p., n.d.], (3013); 9l.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. "Encouragement of study abroad"; [Peking] 1 Sep 1905., (3014); 2l.
  - Miscellanea. Short biography of Edward Rockhill and family., (3015); 2l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript biography of "The Ogle Family"; [n.p., n.d.], (3016); 6l.
    With annotation in hand of Edith Howell (Perkins) Rockhill. Also includes additional material removed from "miscellanea" item (3071).
  - Miscellanea. Typescript Agreement; Peking, 8 Oct 1908., (3017); 7l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript of 3 Articles; [n.p., n.d.], (3018); 3l.
    Includes: Same 3 Articles in French. 2l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript of Schedule of payments of interest and repayments of principal on "Tientsin-Pukow Railway Loan"., (3019); 1l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript Translation of Note addressed by Tsungli Yamen to the Russian Minister, M. de Giers; [n.p.] 1 Jun 1899., (3020); 1l.
    Also: Typescript "Traduction non officielle"; [n.p.] Feb 1910. 1l. In French.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript taken from a letter written by Mrs. Julia L. Michler concerning the "Robeson" genealogy., (3021); 1l.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Document (unsigned) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Patriarcat, 29 Jun 1912., (3022); ([1]p.)
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Article "Affairs of Tibet"; [n.p.] Jul [?], (3023); [2]p.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript of Telegram from Japanese Minister at Peking; [n.p., n.d.], (3024); 1l.
    With ms. annotation.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Articles on slavery; [n.p., n.d.], (3025); [34]p.
  - Miscellanea. A.L.(unsigned) to [?]; Philadelphia, Aug 1835., (3026); ([5]p.)
    Not located at time of endprocessing in August of 2003.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Article on slavery; [n.p., n.d.], (3027); 1l.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Article; [n.p., n.d.], (3028); 1l.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Article; [n.p., n.d.], (3029); 2l.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Articles on slavery; [n.p., n.d.], (3030); [4]p.
  - Miscellanea. Transcript Translation of "The Sermon of the Buddha on the Growing rice" [n.p., n.d.], (3031); 2l.
    Indludes: Typescript of same sermon. 20l.
  - Miscellanea. Translated transcript on "The sermon on growing rice"; [n.p., n.d.], (3032); 5l.
  - Miscellanea. Transcript Translation of "The Sermon on growing rice"; [n.p., n.d.], (3033); 18l.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Fragment., (3034); 1l.
  - Miscellanea. Transcript "The Great Buddhist Sanctuary of North China"; [n.p., n.d.], (3035); 8l.
    Also: Ms. Notes. [6]p.
  - Omitted from this series., (3036)
  - Miscellanea. Typescript Death Announcement., (3037); 2l.
    Also: Typescript "Ceremonies". 1l.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Account "From Watsons Annals of [Philadelphia]"; [n.p., n.d.], (3038); [2]p.
    Also: Typescript "Corrections Remarks"; Paris, 7 Jul 1890. 1l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript Agreement s.(Shu) for construction and management of the Chinese Eastern Railway; [n.p.] 8 Sep 1896., (3039); ([5]p.)
  - Miscellanea. Typescript model of Proposed Edict (or Agreement) for improving the Hwang-Pu River; [n.p.] 3 Mar 1875., (3040); 9l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Regulations for a National Bank"; [n.p., n.d.], (3041); 12l.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Documents; [n.p., n.d.], (3042); 31l.
    In Chinese. With envelopes.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Notes and "Additional Treaties"; [n.p., n.d.], (3043); 2l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescripts of "Treaties, conventions, agreements, protocols; declarations, arrangements, etc."; [n.p., n.d.], (3044); 8l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript Agreement between Jui Cheng, and the Hongkong and Shanghai Banking Corporation; Hankow, 14 Aug 1911., (3045); 9l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript Memorandum translated from Chinese; Peking, 3 May 1911., (3046); 6l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript of Note (unsigned); [n.p.] 24 Feb 1911., (3047); ([3]p.)
  - Miscellanea. Typescript of Notes exchanged between the Wai Wu Pu and the Russian Minister; [n.p., n.d.], (3048); 1l.
    Also: Typescript of Agreement; Peking, 6 Jul 1909. 19l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript Arrangement concerning the acquisition by French Missionaries of land or house property in the interior of China; [n.p., n.d.], (3049); 1l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript Agreement relating to Chientao; Peking, 4 Sep 1909., (3050); ([3]p.)
  - Miscellanea. Typescript agreement concerning mines and railways in Manchuria; Peking, 4 Sep 1909., (3051); ([2]p.)
  - Miscellanea. Typescript Translation "Memorial and Supplements"; [n.p.] 7 Jan 1907., (3052); 7l.
  - Miscellanea. Printed receipt for Telegram filled out in ms.; [n.p., n.d.], (3053); 1l.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Article; [n.p., n.d.] In Turkish., (3054)
    Not located during endprocessing in August of 2003.
  - Miscellanea. Account book filled out in ms.; [n.p., n.d.], (3055); [7]p.
  - Miscellanea. Invitation to dinner with Sun Pao-chi; [n.p., n.d.], (3056); 1l.
  - Miscellanea. A.L. from Yuan Shih Kai; [n.p., Jun 1913], (3057); 4l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Memorial and Edict on Constitutional Government"; [n.p.] 27 Aug 1908., (3058); 20l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript (c.c.) "Standards of Weights and Measures;" [n.p.] 29 Aug 1908., (3059); 18l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Regulations for the joint Chinese and Japanese company for the exploitation of the Yalu Timber"; Mukden, 11 Sep 1908., (3060); 6l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Telegraph Convention"; Tokyo, 12 Oct 1908., (3061); 4l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript translation of note of German Foreign Office; [Berlin, 19 Apr 1902], (3062); 3l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Provincial Deliberative Assemblies," [n.p. ] 22 Jul 1908., (3063); 26l.
    Pages 8 to 20 are wanting.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Establishment of an Office for the Investigation of Governmental Methods"; [n.p.] 6 Jun [1906]., (3064); 1l.
    With Ms. annotation.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Memorial"; [Peking] 12 Mar 1908., (3065); 2l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript translation "Abstract of Memorial"; [Peking] 22 Jul 1908., (3066); 2l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript (c.c.); [n.p., n.d.], (3067); 2l.
    The first two pages of this article are wanting.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript (c.c.) of what purports to be the text of a Treaty signed in 1896. by Russia and China; [n.p., n.d.], (3068); 2l.
  - Miscellanea. Typed (c.c.) Memorandum; Washington, 8 Feb 1910., (3069); 5l.
  - Miscellanea. Ms. Memo concerning Indemnity to be paid by China; Peking, 25 Mar 1901., (3070); [12]p.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Prohibition of Opium"; [Peking] 26 Jun 1907., (3071); 2l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript Memorandum concerning mines along the line of the Antung-Mukden Railway; [n.p., n.d.], (3072); 2l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Regulations for the Establishment at Harbin of a General Bureau to Control International matters in connection with the Railway Co."; [n.p., 1907], (3073); 3l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript (c.c.) "Regulations for the Re-organization of the Provincial Governments of China"; [Peking] 7 Jul 1907., (3074); 22l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Macao-Canton Railway Convention"; Shanghai, 11 Nov 1904., (3075); 14l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Substance of Supplementary Convention between Japan and China"; [n.p., 1903], (3076); 7l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Russo-Chinese Convention"; Mukden, 1903., (3077); 4l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Points to be embodied in instructions sent to the Delegate of the United States on Commission of Bankers at Shanghai"; [n.p., n.d.], (3078); 4l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript from "The North China Herald"; [n.p.] 27 Jan 1912., (3079); 3l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript from "The North China Herald"; [n.p.] 20 Jan 1913., (3080); 4l.
  - Miscellanea. Typescript "Free translation from "Outlines of Rus so-Mongolian trade'"; [n.p., n.d.], (3081); 7l.
  - Miscellanea. 26 Calling Cards from various people. Some in Chinese and others in Chinese and English. Also includes two letters to Rockhill? in Tibet? characters found loose with the diaries., (3082)
  - Miscellanea., (3082a)
    Items found during endprocessing in August of 2003 (in unnumbered folders marked "Miscellanea") have been put in this folder.
- IV. Diaries, account book, and commonplace book
  - Rockhill, Thomas C. A. Diary by Thomas C. Rockhill, Senior; 16 Nov 1834- 21 Apr 1839. Booklet, (3083); [59]p. in 1 v.
    *46M-386A
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Diary; 1 Jan 1908- 31 Dec 1908. Notebook, (3084); [128]p. in 1 v.
    *46M-386B.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Diary; 1 Jan-31 Dec 1909. Notebook, (3085); [381]p. in 1 v.
    *46M-386C.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Diary; 1 Jan-31 Dec. 1910. Booklet, (3086); [368]p. in 1 v.
    *46M-386D.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Diary; 1 Jan-31 Dec 1911. Notebook, (3087); [371]p. in 1 v.
    *46M-386E.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Diary; 1 Jan-31 Dec 1912. Notebook, (3088); [374]p. in 1 v.
    *46M-386F.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Notes; 16 Jun 1912. Notebook, (3089); [10]p.
    Includes: Two photographs.
    *46M-386G.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Diary; 1 Jan 1913- 31 Dec 1913. Notebook, (3090); [182]p. in 1 v.
    *46M-386H.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Diary; 24 Nov-7 Dec 1913. Notebook, (3091); [105]p. in 1 v.
    *46M-386I.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Diary; 30 Mar-7 Jun 1914. Notebook, (3092); [33]p. in 1 v.
    *46M-386J.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. Engraved Memorial to William Woodville Rockhill s.(Willard Straight, and 15 others)., (3093); ([5]p.) in 1v.
    *46M-386K.
  - Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. A. Common-place book of Thomas C. Rockhill; Philadelphia, 1818., (3094); [23]p. in 1 v.
    Includes: Newspaper clippings.
    *46M-386L.
  - Rockhill, Edward Augustus. A. Account Book; Dec 1873-Jun 1875., (3095); [26]p.
    Includes: A.L.s.(James Reily) to General Lyson; London, 16 Sep 1845. ([4]p.) Also: A. Poem entitled "Acrostic" by Thomas C. Rockhill, Senior. 1l. Also includes map of Geryville, Jun 1874.
    *46M-386M.
- V. Letterbooks
  - Letter-book of 505l. containing copies of Typed LL.s. to various people; 1894-1896 Dec. 17 - Sep. 11., (3096); 1 v.
    Shelved with item (3097).
    *46M-386N.
  - Letter-book of 503l. containing copies of Typed LL.s. to various people; 1896-1897 Sept. 14 - May 10., (3097); 1 v.
    Includes: A.LL.s. to various people and A.Accounts to the U.S. Government; 1885-1888.
    Shelved with item (3096).
    *46M-386O.
  - Letter-book of 500l. (478 of them blank) of Memoranda; 1897 Mar. 10-26., (3098); 1 v.
    *46M-386P.
  - Letter-book of 1020l. containing copies of Typed LL.s. to various people; 1899-1903 May 22 - Dec. 28., (3099); 1 v.
    *46M-386Q.
  - Letter-book of 500l. (435 of them blank) containing Typed and A.LL.s. to various people; 1900-1901 Sept. 6-Feb. 16., (3100); 1 v.
    *46M-386R.
  - Letter-book of 1014l. (206 of them blank) containing copies of Typed LL.s. to various people; 1902-1905 Jan. 15 - Mar. 21., (3101); 1 v.
    *46M-386S.
  - Letter-book of 498l. (122 of them blank) containing copies of Typed LL.s. to various people; 1903-1905 Dec. 30 - Mar. 24., (3102); 1 v.
    *46M-386T.
- VI. Card index to Rockhill Papers
  - [Index to the papers of William Woodville Rockhill]., (3103); 7 card file boxes.
    Arranged chronologically.
    *46M-386U.